# Michał Alchimowicz

Over 3 years of experience as Front-end Developer. Highly motivated, dedicated to my work and enthusiastic to learn new things. Capable of working with a variety of technology and software solutions. Focused on the goal of further improving knowledge and becoming a Senior Developer.



# **Experience**

# 2018-04 Wakacje.pl S.A

Front-end Developer

- Rewriting a legacy app and migrating to a new tech stack (from PHP, ES5, jQuery, Smart to React, MobX, Next.js, Node and ES6),
- Deployment to Production,
- Participating in the full lifecycle delivery,
- Working closely with the product and UX team members,
- Working on new frontend features,
- Writing unit, integration and e2e tests (Jest, Enzyme, Cypress).

## 2017-01 - Wakacje.pl S.A

2018-03

Junior Front-end Developer

- Implementing new features with clean, simple and tested code,
- · Refactoring and improving existing code,
- Working closely with UX and content team members.

### 2016-08 - Stukot Pikseli, Gdańsk

2016-10

Junior Front-end Developer

- Cutting and codding website templates provided by graphic designers,
- · Developing and optimizing of already active websites,
- Permanent cooperation with graphic designers and developers.

# 2015-03 - Combidata Poland (Asseco), Gdynia

2015-09

Recruitment Assistant

- · Contracting with clients,
- Verifying recruitment documentation,
- Completing and proofreading recruitment documentation,
- Monitoring circulation and archiving documents,
- Passing on verified documentation to the Office of Projects and preparing
- the documentation for postal shipment,
- Drafting confirmations of training completion,
- Other recruitment tasks commissioned by supervisors.

### **2009-04 - United Parcel Service, Gdańsk**

2014-04

Operations employee

- Clarifying / establishing address details of package recipients,
- Preparing operations reports,
- Using special software available at the workplace,

"I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)".



#### Address

Angielska Grobla 16/3A 80-756 Gdańsk

### **Phone**

+48 500-431-092

#### E-mail

michalalchimowicz@gmail.com

#### Place of birth

Gdańsk

#### Date of birth

1986-09-16

#### Git

https://github.com/Manjado

#### LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/malchimowicz



JavaScript (ES5,ES6)

TypeScript (in progress)

React

MobX

Redux (in progress)

Node.js (Express, Next.js)

HTML

CSS

Python



English

Portuguese



Contacting UPS facilities in Poland and abroad.

## 2008-01 - United Parcel Service, Gdańsk

### 2009-03

Customer Service

- Investigating and resolving customer enquirers,
- Problem solving and offering solutions to meet the customers needs,
- Answering incoming phone calls and e-mails,
- Contacting UPS facilities in Poland and abroad,
- Identifying and resolving delivery problem in a timely manner.

### 2006-09 - United Parcel Service, Gdańsk

#### 2007-12

Warehouseman

- Unload / load parcels from vehicles maintaining high activity level whilst using safe working methods,
- · Assisting in the electronic scanning of all parcels using a handheld scanner,
- Using special software available at the workplace.

# **Education**

2005-10 -

Ateneum University in Gdańsk, Poland, Journalism and Communication,

2008-06

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.)



# Courses

2016-04 -

Stationary course - JavaScript & Node.js - 42h,Gdańsk.

2016-06



# References

Combidata Poland - available on request,

UPS Polska - available on request.

# (7)

# Interests

**Programming** 

Traveling

Capoeira

"I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)".